revenueuniverse.com 2009-04-30

# 

This privacy policy shall constitute the entire agreement between Revenue Universe, a property of The Free4Me Network, LLC, and you governing the collection and use of your personal information at the http://revenueuniverse.com/ website and/or participation as an affiliate member in the Revenue Universe affiliate or merchant program.  

**Terms and Definitions**

This privacy policy terms the phrases "us", "we", "the company", "the site", "the program", "Revenue Universe" as the network and website owners and employees. Terms defined as "you", "member", "Affiliate", "Merchant", "user" defines anyone utilizing this website. This includes employees and representatives of your company, corporation, LLC, all all business entities.   

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time, at our sole discretion, use of this website constitutes your acceptance of the current Privacy Policy. Changes may include, without limitation, changes in the types of information we collect and how we use such information. If you do not agree to any changes to the Privacy Policy, you must discontinue your use of the website immediately. By visiting, accessing and/or using the website and/or your continued participation in the program, you are fully subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time.

**Information Collection and Use**

Since we are an affiliate network program, we attempt to only collect personal information from 1) persons over the age of majority or business entities that 2) own and operate websites through which they conduct a business. Other then log a Visitor’s visit to the Program Website, we do not collect personally identifiable information about or from Visitors who do nothing more than visit the Program Website and fail to supply personal information to us.  

**Applicants**  

Revenue Universe collects personal information from each and every applicant for purposes of evaluating the applicant’s enrollment as a member into Revenue Universe.  The personal information collected from applicants is principally intended for verification and administrative purposes, should the applicant be accepted as a member. Submission of your personal information constitutes the agreement that we may contact you via phone, email or postal mail to verify information submitted, send information regarding the use of the program or contact at our discretion. All information submitted to Revenue Universe is verified secure and protected with up to a 256-bit secure sockets layer protection.  

All applications to become a member are subject to Revenue Universe's acceptance. We reserve the right to accept or refuse any application at our discretion. If we reject your application, then we may retain your personal information that you supplied in your application and use same in accordance with this privacy policy. If you are rejected from the program, you agree to receive a notice via email, phone or postal mail regarding such. If you do not agree, cease use of this site immediately.  

**Members**  

If we accept your application as a member, we will use and share your personal information with third parties in any manner consistent with the practices of the program as outlined in this privacy policy. This may include volume of leads generated, website URL, email address and other personally identifiable information as required to carry out the function of the program. All personal information collected is verified secure and protected with up to a 256-bit secure sockets layer protection. We retain the personal information collected even if that member leaves the program. Revenue Universe is not responsible or liable for any use or disclosure by any third party of any member personal information that we furnish to such third party. In addition, Revenue Universe reserves the right to share current or past applicant and/or member information in the event Revenue Universe believes that the program and/or account is being or has been used in violation of the Terms and Conditions, if the member is using their account in an illegal or fraudulent manner, if the information is ordered by a court of law, if Revenue Universe is sold or acquired, or when Revenue Universe deems it appropriate. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when Revenue Universe, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate. If you do not agree, cease use of this site immediately.  

**Marketing**  

In addition to other uses outlined in this policy, the information that applicants and members submit to Revenue Universe may be used in conjunction with this program to contact you regarding the program, your account or other reasons deemed appropriate by Revenue Universe. By applying to be a Member with the Program, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq.  Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the FTC's Do-Not-Call List, Revenue Universe retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq.. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the website, such action shall constitute an inquiry and/or application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. and you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq.

**Collective Data  **

Revenue Universe may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the website. This may include, but not limited to, your browser type, operating system, and internet service provider. Collection of this data will be used for statistical reasons, website improvement and other reasons deemed necessary by Revenue Universe.  

**Cookies**

When a Member logs into their account, a "cookie" is placed on their computer. A cookie is a unique piece of code and/or text that is issued to the member and placed on the computer's hard drive. Cookies are not harmful to your computer. Cookies are required to view this website and to utilize this program.  

**Privacy Policies of Member Websites**

Revenue Universe requires, as part of its program, that each member have an retain a visible privacy policy on their website. Removal of such privacy policy can result in Revenue Universe closing your member account. Members are responsible for outlining a privacy policy appropriate to their visitors and users. Revenue Universe bears no responsibility, legally or financially, for the lack of an appropriate privacy policy displayed by it's members or by data collected.  

**Minors**

Individuals under 18 years of age are not allowed to apply for the program. If you are under the legal age of 18 years old do not apply for or submit any personal information to this website. If you are under the age of 18 years old, cease use of this website immediately.

**Advertiser and Third Party Websites**

Revenue Universe bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.  

**Contact Us**

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or the program, please contact us via email at: support@revenueuniverse.com.
